<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Get Dunked</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="AhriLore" formatted="false">Unlike other foxes that roamed the woods of southern Ionia, Ahri had always felt a strange connection to the magical
    world around her; a connection that was somehow incomplete. Deep inside, she felt the skin she had been born into was
    an ill fit for her and dreamt of one day becoming human. Her goal seemed forever out of reach, until she happened upon
    the wake of a human battle. It was a grisly scene, the land obscured by the forms of wounded and dying soldiers. She
    felt drawn to one: a robed man encircled by a waning field of magic whose life was quickly slipping away. She
    approached him and something deep inside of her triggered, reaching out to the man in a way she couldn\'t understand.
    His life essence poured into her, carried on invisible strands of magic. The sensation was intoxicating and
    overwhelming. As her reverie faded, she was delighted to discover that she had changed. Her sleek white fur had
    receded and her body was long and lithe, the shape of the humans who lay scattered about her.\n\n
    However, though she appeared human, she knew that in truth the transformation was incomplete. A cunning creature,
    she adapted herself to the customs of human society and used her profound gift of beauty to attract unsuspecting men.
    She could consume their life essences when they were under the spell of her seductive charms. Feeding on their
    desires brought her closer to her dream, but as she took more lives, a strange sense of regret began to well within
    her. She had reservations about actions which never troubled her as a fox. She realized that she could not overcome
    the pangs of her evolving morality. In search of a solution, Ahri found the Institute of War, home of the most gifted
    mages on Runeterra. They offered her a chance to attain her humanity without further harm through service in the League
    of Legends.\n\n\t"Mercy is a human luxury... and responsibility."\n\t
    ―Ahri</string>
    <string name="EssenceTheft">    Ahri gains a charge of Essence Theft with each enemy unit hit by any of her spells, with a cap of 3 
    charges per spell cast. Upon reaching 9 charges, Ahri\'s next spell will have 35% bonus spell vamp.</string>
    <string name="OrbOfDeception">ACTIVE: Ahri sends out an orb in a line in front of her and then pulls it back, 
  dealing magic damage on the way out and true damage on the way back.</string>
    <string name="FoxFire">    ACTIVE: Ahri releases three fox-fires to surround her for up to 5 seconds. 
    After a short delay after cast, each flame will target the closest enemy unit to itself, 
    prioritizing champions, and deal magic damage to the target.
    Additional fox-fires that hit the same target will only deal 50% damage.</string>
    <string name="Charm">    ACTIVE: Ahri will blow a kiss that travels in a line in front of her. It will deal magic damage and charm 
    the first enemy it encounters, forcing them to walk harmlessly towards her, while being slowed by 50% for 
    the duration.</string>
    <string name="SpiritRush">    ACTIVE: Ahri dashes towards the cursor and fires essence bolts, dealing magic damage to up to 3 
    nearby enemies, prioritizing champions. In the next 10 seconds, Spirit Rush can be cast two additional 
    times before going on cooldown. Each enemy can only be hit once per dash.</string>
    <string name="TwinDisciplines" formatted="false">    DISCIPLINE OF FORCE: Akali\'s auto attacks deal 6% (+ 1% per 6 AP) bonus magic damage.\nDISCIPLINE OF MIGHT: 
    Akali gains 6% (+ 1% per 6 bonus AD) spell vamp.</string>
    <string name="MarkOfTheAssassin">    ACTIVE: Akali throws her kama at a target enemy, dealing magic damage and marking the target for 6 seconds.
    Akali\'s basic attacks or Crescent Slashes against a marked target will consume the mark, dealing the same damage 
    again and restoring energy to Akali.</string>
    <string name="TwilightShroud">    ACTIVE: Akali creates a smoke cloud in the target 600-diameter area for 8 seconds. While within the cloud,
    Akali is granted stealth, and bonus armor and magic resistance. Attacking or using abilities reveals her for 0.5 seconds. 
    Enemies inside the smoke suffer slowed movement.</string>
    <string name="CrescentSlash">    ACTIVE: Akali flourishes her kamas, dealing physical damage and triggering any Marks of the Assassin on nearby enemies.</string>
    <string name="ShadowDance">    ACTIVE: Akali uses an Essence of Shadow, dashing to and dealing magic damage to a target enemy. Akali gains an Essence of Shadow 
    periodically, affected by cooldown reduction, up to a maximum of 3. Additionally, Akali gains an Essence of Shadow for each kill or
    assist she obtains.</string>
    <string name="Trample">    Each time Alistar casts a spell, for 3 seconds afterwards he gains the ability to ignore unit collision and will 
    deal 3 + (1 × level) (+ 10% AP) magic damage to nearby enemy units and structures each second. Trample deals double damage to minions 
    and monsters.</string>
    <string name="Pulverize">    ACTIVE: Alistar smashes the ground where he is standing, dealing magic damage to all surrounding enemies and knocking them up 
    for 1 second, additionally stunning them upon landing for 0.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Headbutt">    ACTIVE: Alistar dashes to an enemy\'s position and rams them, dealing magic damage and knocking them back a set distance over 
    1 second, also briefly immobilizing them.</string>
    <string name="TriumphantRoar">    ACTIVE: Alistar instantly restores health to himself, healing nearby friendly units for half of that amount. The cooldown 
    of this ability is reduced by 2 seconds each time a nearby enemy unit dies.</string>
    <string name="UnbreakableWill">    ACTIVE: With a mighty roar Alistar removes all crowd control effects on himself, and for 7 seconds afterwards he gains 
    bonus attack damage and takes reduced physical and magic damage.</string>
    <string name="CursedTouch">Amumu\'s autoattacks reduce the target\'s magic resistance by 15 / 20 / 25 for 3 seconds. The debuff
  doesn\'t stack but it refreshes with every autoattack.</string>
    <string name="BandageToss">ACTIVE: Amumu tosses a sticky bandage in a straight line towards a target location. If it contacts an enemy, 
  Amumu will pull himself to it, dealing magic damage and stunning the target for 1 second.</string>
    <string name="Despair">TOGGLE: While toggled on, Amumu will be surrounded by a small damaging area of tears. Enemies in the area will be dealt 
  a percentage of their maximum health plus a base amount as magic damage each second.</string>
    <string name="Tantrum" formatted="false">    PASSIVE: Amumu takes reduced physical damage from autoattacks and abilities.\nACTIVE: Amumu will make an instantaneous tantrum, 
    dealing magic damage to surrounding units. Additionally, each time Amumu is hit by an autoattack the cooldown on Tantrum\'s active 
    will be reduced by 0.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="CurseOfTheSadMummy">    ACTIVE: Amumu entangles surrounding enemy units, dealing magic damage and rendering them unable to move or use autoattacks for 2 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Rebirth">    Upon dying, Anivia will transform into an egg and will get an armor and magic resistance modifier of −40 / −25 / −10 / +5 / +20. 
    If the egg can survive for 6 seconds, she is reborn with the same percentage of health that her egg had left. 
    Rebirth has a static cooldown and is unaffected by cooldown reduction.</string>
    <string name="FlashFrost">    ACTIVE: Anivia fires an orb of ice that travels in a line. All enemies it hits take magic damage and are "chilled" for 3 seconds, 
    slowing their movement speed by 20%. The shard will detonate when reaching its maximum range or if the ability is activated again. 
    When the shard explodes, it deals the same damage to all enemies within 75 range, stuns them for 1 second, and "chills" them for 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Crystallize">    ACTIVE: Anivia creates an impassible wall of ice centered on target point, perpendicular to Anivia\'s facing, lasting 5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Frostbite">ACTIVE: Anivia fires a shard of ice to deal magic damage to a target enemy. Frostbite deals double damage 
  to enemies "chilled" by Anivia\'s other spells.</string>
    <string name="GlacialStorm">    TOGGLE: Anivia creates a blizzard in a target area. Enemies inside this area take magic damage over time and 
    are "chilled", slowing their movement and attack speed by 20%. Glacial Storm drains mana from Anivia while active, and deactivates 
    if she runs out.</string>
    <string name="Pyromania">    After every 4 spell casts, Annie\'s next offensive spell will stun all damaged enemies for 1.75 seconds. The stunning 
    spell does not count towards Pyromania\'s counter.</string>
    <string name="Disintegrate">    ACTIVE: Annie deals magic damage to a target enemy. If Disintegrate kills the target, it refunds its mana cost.</string>
    <string name="Incinerate">    ACTIVE: Annie deals magic damage to all enemies in a cone in front of her.</string>
    <string name="MoltenShield">    ACTIVE: For 5 seconds, Annie has increased armor and magic resistance and deals magic damage to enemies 
    whenever they use a basic attack against her.</string>
    <string name="SummonTibbers">    ACTIVE: Annie summons Tibbers to the target location in a burst of flame, dealing magic damage to enemies 
    within range. Tibbers remains on the field for up to 45 seconds, and Annie can control his movement and his 
    physical attacks. Tibbers is also surrounded by a flaming aura that deals magic damage every second to enemies 
    around himself.</string>
    <string name="Focus">    Ashe\'s critical strike chance increases by 3 / 6 / 9 / 12 / 15 / 18% every 3 seconds while not attacking. Focus\' 
    bonus is expended with her next basic attack.</string>
    <string name="FrostShot">    TOGGLE: Ashe\'s basic attacks slow her targets for 2 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Volley">    ACTIVE: Ashe fires 7 arrows in a cone, dealing physical damage to each target hit. Each arrow will only hit 
    one enemy, and each enemy will only be hit by one arrow. Volley also applies the current rank of Frost Shot, 
    regardless if it is toggled on or not.</string>
    <string name="Hawkshot" formatted="false">    PASSIVE: Ashe gains bonus gold whenever she kills a unit or destroys a structure. \nACTIVE: Ashe animates a hawk to scout for her, 
    revealing terrain for 2 seconds as it flies towards a target location. Hawkshot reveals a wide area for 5 seconds 
    when it reaches its destination.</string>
    <string name="EnchantedCrystalArrow">    ACTIVE: Ashe fires a large arrow in a straight line. If it hits an enemy champion, it will deal magic damage and stun 
    that champion for 1 to 3.5 seconds based on the distance the arrow traveled. Additionally, surrounding units take half the 
    damage and are slowed by 50% for 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="ManaBarrier" formatted="false">    PASSIVE: When Blitzcrank\'s life is brought below 20%  health he activates Mana Barrier, creating a damage shield that lasts for 
    10 seconds. The shield strength is equal to 50% of Blitzcrank\'s current mana.</string>
    <string name="RocketGrab">    ACTIVE: Blitzcrank fires his right hand at a straight line to the target area. If his hand encounters an enemy unit it will 
    pull the target back to his location, dealing magic damage and stunning it for 1 second in the process.</string>
    <string name="Overdrive">    ACTIVE: Blitzcrank super charges himself to gain dramatically increased movement and attack speed for 8 seconds.</string>
    <string name="PowerFist">    ACTIVE: Blitzcrank charges up his fist to make his next attack deal double his total attack damage and knock his 
    target up in the air. This ability will reset Blitzcrank\'s attack timer when cast.</string>
    <string name="StaticField" formatted="false">    PASSIVE: Every 2.5 seconds, Blitzcrank fires a lightning bolt at one random nearby enemy unit, dealing magic
    damage to it. This is not affected by cooldown reduction, and will not target enemies in stealth.\nACTIVE: Blitzcrank emits a wave of 
    electricity to deal magic damage to nearby enemies and silence them for 0.5 seconds. Activating it removes the passive lightning 
    bolts until Static Field becomes available again.</string>
    <string name="Blaze" formatted="false">    Brand\'s spells light his targets ablaze, dealing 2% of their maximum health as magic damage per second for 4 seconds, 
    for a total of 8%. Monsters take a maximum of 80 damage per second from Blaze.</string>
    <string name="Sear">    ACTIVE: Brand launches a fireball forward that deals magic damage to the first enemy it hits. 
    If the target is ablaze, the target will be stunned for 2 seconds.</string>
    <string name="PillarOfFlame" formatted="false">    ACTIVE: After a short delay, Brand blasts a target area, dealing magic damage to enemy 
    units within the area. Units that are ablaze take an additional 25% damage.</string>
    <string name="Conflagration">    ACTIVE: Brand conjures an instant blast at his target, dealing magic damage to it. If the target is ablaze, 
    the conflagration will also spread to nearby enemies.</string>
    <string name="Pyroclasm">    ACTIVE: Brand unleashes a devastating torrent of fire to a target that will bounce between enemies, dealing damage each 
    time it bounces. If a target is ablaze, Pyroclasm\'s next bounce will prioritize champions. It will bounce up to four
    times for a total of five hits, and can hit the same enemy up to three times.</string>
    <string name="ChampionsButton">Champions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_champs">Champions</string>
    <string name="title_section3">lore</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Abilities</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Statistics</string>
    <string name="title_activity_champion_page">ChampionName</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Other</string>
    <string name="title_activity_stats">StatsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ability_fragment">AbilityFragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lore_fragment">LoreFragment</string>

    <string-array name="ChampNames">
        <item>Ahri</item>
        <item>Akali</item>
        <item>Alistar</item>
        <item>Amumu</item>
        <item>Anivia</item>
        <item>Annie</item>
        <item>Ashe</item>
        <item>Blitzcrank</item>
        <item>Brand</item>
        <item>Caitlyn</item>
        <item>Cassiopeia</item>
        <item>Cho\'Gath</item>
        <item>Corki</item>
        <item>Darius</item>
        <item>Diana</item>
        <item>Dr. Mundo</item>
        <item>Draven</item>
        <item>Elise</item>
        <item>Evelynn</item>
        <item>Ezreal</item>
        <item>Fiddlesticks</item>
        <item>Fiora</item>
        <item>Fizz</item>
        <item>Galio</item>
        <item>Gangplank</item>
        <item>Garen</item>
        <item>Gragas</item>
        <item>Graves</item>
        <item>Hecarim</item>
        <item>Heimerdinger</item>
        <item>Irelia</item>
        <item>Janna</item>
        <item>Jarvan IV</item>
        <item>Jax</item>
        <item>Jayce</item>
        <item>Karma</item>
        <item>Karthus</item>
        <item>Kassadin</item>
        <item>Katarina</item>
        <item>Kayle</item>
        <item>Kennen</item>
        <item>Kha\'Zix</item>
        <item>Kog\'Maw</item>
        <item>LeBlanc</item>
        <item>Lee Sin</item>
        <item>Leona</item>
        <item>Lulu</item>
        <item>Lux</item>
        <item>Malphite</item>
        <item>Malzahar</item>
        <item>Maokai</item>
        <item>Master Yi</item>
        <item>Miss Fortune</item>
        <item>Mordekaiser</item>
        <item>Morgana</item>
        <item>Nami</item>
        <item>Nasus</item>
        <item>Nautilus</item>
        <item>Nidalee</item>
        <item>Nocturne</item>
        <item>Nunu</item>
        <item>Olaf</item>
        <item>Orianna</item>
        <item>Pantheon</item>
        <item>Poppy</item>
        <item>Quinn</item>
        <item>Rammus</item>
        <item>Renekton</item>
        <item>Rengar</item>
        <item>Riven</item>
        <item>Rumble</item>
        <item>Ryze</item>
        <item>Sejuani</item>
        <item>Shaco</item>
        <item>Shen</item>
        <item>Shyvana</item>
        <item>Singed</item>
        <item>Sion</item>
        <item>Sivir</item>
        <item>Skarner</item>
        <item>Sona</item>
        <item>Soraka</item>
        <item>Swain</item>
        <item>Syndra</item>
        <item>Talon</item>
        <item>Taric</item>
        <item>Teemo</item>
        <item>Thresh</item>
        <item>Tristana</item>
        <item>Trundle</item>
        <item>Tryndamere</item>
        <item>Twisted Fate</item>
        <item>Twitch</item>
        <item>Udyr</item>
        <item>Urgot</item>
        <item>Varus</item>
        <item>Vayne</item>
        <item>Veigar</item>
        <item>Vi</item>
        <item>Viktor</item>
        <item>Vladimir</item>
        <item>Volibear</item>
        <item>Warwick</item>
        <item>Xerath</item>
        <item>Xin Zhao</item>
        <item>Yorick</item>
        <item>Zed</item>
        <item>Ziggs</item>
        <item>Zilean</item>
        <item>Zyra</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_profile">ProfileActivity</string>

</resources>