<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Get Dunked</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="BloodWell" formatted="false">Whenever Aatrox uses an ability that costs health, he stores 100% of the health 
        cost into his Blood Well. The maximum amount of health the Blood Well can store is 30 + (45 × level). 
        If Aatrox has not dealt or received damage in the last 5 seconds, his Blood Well will deplete at a rate of 2% per second.
        \n\nUpon taking fatal damage, Blood Well activates and places Aatrox in stasis for 3 seconds.
         Over the stasis duration the Blood Well is emptied and Aatrox restores health equal to its contents plus 10.5 + (15.75 × level). 
         Blood Well\'s activation has a static cooldown and is unaffected by cooldown reduction.\n\nAlso, 
         Aatrox passively increases his attack speed by 1% for every 2% in the Blood Well.</string>
    <string name="DarkFlight" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Aatrox takes flight and slams down at a targeted area, 
        dealing physical damage to nearby enemies upon landing. Enemies in the center of the area are also knocked up for 1 second.</string>
    <string name="BloodThirst" formatted="false">Blood Thirst:\nTOGGLE OFF: Aatrox heals himself on every third attack. 
        If Aatrox is below 50% health he will heal for three times as much.\n\nBlood Price:\nTOGGLE ON: Aatrox deals bonus physical 
        damage on every third attack at the cost of health.</string>
    <string name="BladesofTorment" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Aatrox unleashes and sends forward the power of his blade, 
        dealing magic damage to enemies in a line and slowing them by 40% for a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="Massacre" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Aatrox draws in the blood of his foes, dealing magic damage to nearby enemy champions.\n\nFor 
        the next 12 seconds, Aatrox gains bonus attack speed and 175 bonus attack range (325 total range). 
        His attacks are still considered melee.</string>
    <string name="AhriLore" formatted="false">Unlike other foxes that roamed the woods of southern Ionia, Ahri had always felt a strange connection to the magical
    world around her; a connection that was somehow incomplete. Deep inside, she felt the skin she had been born into was
    an ill fit for her and dreamt of one day becoming human. Her goal seemed forever out of reach, until she happened upon
    the wake of a human battle. It was a grisly scene, the land obscured by the forms of wounded and dying soldiers. She
    felt drawn to one: a robed man encircled by a waning field of magic whose life was quickly slipping away. She
    approached him and something deep inside of her triggered, reaching out to the man in a way she couldn\'t understand.
    His life essence poured into her, carried on invisible strands of magic. The sensation was intoxicating and
    overwhelming. As her reverie faded, she was delighted to discover that she had changed. Her sleek white fur had
    receded and her body was long and lithe, the shape of the humans who lay scattered about her.\n\n
    However, though she appeared human, she knew that in truth the transformation was incomplete. A cunning creature,
    she adapted herself to the customs of human society and used her profound gift of beauty to attract unsuspecting men.
    She could consume their life essences when they were under the spell of her seductive charms. Feeding on their
    desires brought her closer to her dream, but as she took more lives, a strange sense of regret began to well within
    her. She had reservations about actions which never troubled her as a fox. She realized that she could not overcome
    the pangs of her evolving morality. In search of a solution, Ahri found the Institute of War, home of the most gifted
    mages on Runeterra. They offered her a chance to attain her humanity without further harm through service in the League
    of Legends.\n\n\t"Mercy is a human luxury... and responsibility."\n\t
    ―Ahri</string>
    <string name="EssenceTheft" formatted="false">    Ahri gains a charge of Essence Theft with each enemy unit hit by any of her spells, with a cap of 3 
    charges per spell cast. Upon reaching 9 charges, Ahri\'s next spell will have 35% bonus spell vamp.</string>
    <string name="OrbOfDeception">ACTIVE: Ahri sends out an orb in a line in front of her and then pulls it back, 
  dealing magic damage on the way out and true damage on the way back.</string>
    <string name="FoxFire">    ACTIVE: Ahri releases three fox-fires to surround her for up to 5 seconds. 
    After a short delay after cast, each flame will target the closest enemy unit to itself, 
    prioritizing champions, and deal magic damage to the target.
    Additional fox-fires that hit the same target will only deal 50% damage.</string>
    <string name="Charm" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Ahri will blow a kiss that travels in a line in front of her. It will deal magic damage and charm 
    the first enemy it encounters, forcing them to walk harmlessly towards her, while being slowed by 50% for 
    the duration.</string>
    <string name="SpiritRush">    ACTIVE: Ahri dashes towards the cursor and fires essence bolts, dealing magic damage to up to 3 
    nearby enemies, prioritizing champions. In the next 10 seconds, Spirit Rush can be cast two additional 
    times before going on cooldown. Each enemy can only be hit once per dash.</string>
    <string name="TwinDisciplines" formatted="false">    DISCIPLINE OF FORCE: Akali\'s auto attacks deal 6% (+ 1% per 6 AP) bonus magic damage.\nDISCIPLINE OF MIGHT: 
    Akali gains 6% (+ 1% per 6 bonus AD) spell vamp.</string>
    <string name="MarkOfTheAssassin">    ACTIVE: Akali throws her kama at a target enemy, dealing magic damage and marking the target for 6 seconds.
    Akali\'s basic attacks or Crescent Slashes against a marked target will consume the mark, dealing the same damage 
    again and restoring energy to Akali.</string>
    <string name="TwilightShroud">    ACTIVE: Akali creates a smoke cloud in the target 600-diameter area for 8 seconds. While within the cloud,
    Akali is granted stealth, and bonus armor and magic resistance. Attacking or using abilities reveals her for 0.5 seconds. 
    Enemies inside the smoke suffer slowed movement.</string>
    <string name="CrescentSlash">    ACTIVE: Akali flourishes her kamas, dealing physical damage and triggering any Marks of the Assassin on nearby enemies.</string>
    <string name="ShadowDance">    ACTIVE: Akali uses an Essence of Shadow, dashing to and dealing magic damage to a target enemy. Akali gains an Essence of Shadow 
    periodically, affected by cooldown reduction, up to a maximum of 3. Additionally, Akali gains an Essence of Shadow for each kill or
    assist she obtains.</string>
    <string name="Trample">    Each time Alistar casts a spell, for 3 seconds afterwards he gains the ability to ignore unit collision and will 
    deal 3 + (1 × level) (+ 10%% AP) magic damage to nearby enemy units and structures each second. Trample deals double damage to minions 
    and monsters.</string>
    <string name="Pulverize">    ACTIVE: Alistar smashes the ground where he is standing, dealing magic damage to all surrounding enemies and knocking them up 
    for 1 second, additionally stunning them upon landing for 0.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Headbutt">    ACTIVE: Alistar dashes to an enemy\'s position and rams them, dealing magic damage and knocking them back a set distance over 
    1 second, also briefly immobilizing them.</string>
    <string name="TriumphantRoar">    ACTIVE: Alistar instantly restores health to himself, healing nearby friendly units for half of that amount. The cooldown 
    of this ability is reduced by 2 seconds each time a nearby enemy unit dies.</string>
    <string name="UnbreakableWill">    ACTIVE: With a mighty roar Alistar removes all crowd control effects on himself, and for 7 seconds afterwards he gains 
    bonus attack damage and takes reduced physical and magic damage.</string>
    <string name="CursedTouch">Amumu\'s autoattacks reduce the target\'s magic resistance by 15 / 20 / 25 for 3 seconds. The debuff
  doesn\'t stack but it refreshes with every autoattack.</string>
    <string name="BandageToss">ACTIVE: Amumu tosses a sticky bandage in a straight line towards a target location. If it contacts an enemy, 
  Amumu will pull himself to it, dealing magic damage and stunning the target for 1 second.</string>
    <string name="Despair">TOGGLE: While toggled on, Amumu will be surrounded by a small damaging area of tears. Enemies in the area will be dealt 
  a percentage of their maximum health plus a base amount as magic damage each second.</string>
    <string name="Tantrum" formatted="false">    PASSIVE: Amumu takes reduced physical damage from autoattacks and abilities.\nACTIVE: Amumu will make an instantaneous tantrum, 
    dealing magic damage to surrounding units. Additionally, each time Amumu is hit by an autoattack the cooldown on Tantrum\'s active 
    will be reduced by 0.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="CurseOfTheSadMummy">    ACTIVE: Amumu entangles surrounding enemy units, dealing magic damage and rendering them unable to move or use autoattacks for 2 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Rebirth">    Upon dying, Anivia will transform into an egg and will get an armor and magic resistance modifier of −40 / −25 / −10 / +5 / +20. 
    If the egg can survive for 6 seconds, she is reborn with the same percentage of health that her egg had left. 
    Rebirth has a static cooldown and is unaffected by cooldown reduction.</string>
    <string name="FlashFrost">    ACTIVE: Anivia fires an orb of ice that travels in a line. All enemies it hits take magic damage and are "chilled" for 3 seconds, 
    slowing their movement speed by 20%. The shard will detonate when reaching its maximum range or if the ability is activated again. 
    When the shard explodes, it deals the same damage to all enemies within 75 range, stuns them for 1 second, and "chills" them for 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Crystallize">    ACTIVE: Anivia creates an impassible wall of ice centered on target point, perpendicular to Anivia\'s facing, lasting 5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Frostbite">ACTIVE: Anivia fires a shard of ice to deal magic damage to a target enemy. Frostbite deals double damage 
  to enemies "chilled" by Anivia\'s other spells.</string>
    <string name="GlacialStorm">    TOGGLE: Anivia creates a blizzard in a target area. Enemies inside this area take magic damage over time and 
    are "chilled", slowing their movement and attack speed by 20%. Glacial Storm drains mana from Anivia while active, and deactivates 
    if she runs out.</string>
    <string name="Pyromania">    After every 4 spell casts, Annie\'s next offensive spell will stun all damaged enemies for 1.75 seconds. The stunning 
    spell does not count towards Pyromania\'s counter.</string>
    <string name="Disintegrate">    ACTIVE: Annie deals magic damage to a target enemy. If Disintegrate kills the target, it refunds its mana cost.</string>
    <string name="Incinerate">    ACTIVE: Annie deals magic damage to all enemies in a cone in front of her.</string>
    <string name="MoltenShield">    ACTIVE: For 5 seconds, Annie has increased armor and magic resistance and deals magic damage to enemies 
    whenever they use a basic attack against her.</string>
    <string name="SummonTibbers">    ACTIVE: Annie summons Tibbers to the target location in a burst of flame, dealing magic damage to enemies 
    within range. Tibbers remains on the field for up to 45 seconds, and Annie can control his movement and his 
    physical attacks. Tibbers is also surrounded by a flaming aura that deals magic damage every second to enemies 
    around himself.</string>
    <string name="Focus">    Ashe\'s critical strike chance increases by 3 / 6 / 9 / 12 / 15 / 18%% every 3 seconds while not attacking. Focus\' 
    bonus is expended with her next basic attack.</string>
    <string name="FrostShot">    TOGGLE: Ashe\'s basic attacks slow her targets for 2 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Volley">    ACTIVE: Ashe fires 7 arrows in a cone, dealing physical damage to each target hit. Each arrow will only hit 
    one enemy, and each enemy will only be hit by one arrow. Volley also applies the current rank of Frost Shot, 
    regardless if it is toggled on or not.</string>
    <string name="Hawkshot" formatted="false">    PASSIVE: Ashe gains bonus gold whenever she kills a unit or destroys a structure. \nACTIVE: Ashe animates a hawk to scout for her, 
    revealing terrain for 2 seconds as it flies towards a target location. Hawkshot reveals a wide area for 5 seconds 
    when it reaches its destination.</string>
    <string name="EnchantedCrystalArrow">ACTIVE: Ashe fires a large arrow in a straight line. If it hits an enemy champion, it will deal magic damage and stun 
    that champion for 1 to 3.5 seconds based on the distance the arrow traveled. Additionally, surrounding units take half the 
    damage and are slowed by 50%% for 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="ManaBarrier" formatted="false">    PASSIVE: When Blitzcrank\'s life is brought below 20%  health he activates Mana Barrier, creating a damage shield that lasts for 
    10 seconds. The shield strength is equal to 50% of Blitzcrank\'s current mana.</string>
    <string name="RocketGrab">    ACTIVE: Blitzcrank fires his right hand at a straight line to the target area. If his hand encounters an enemy unit it will 
    pull the target back to his location, dealing magic damage and stunning it for 1 second in the process.</string>
    <string name="Overdrive">    ACTIVE: Blitzcrank super charges himself to gain dramatically increased movement and attack speed for 8 seconds.</string>
    <string name="PowerFist">    ACTIVE: Blitzcrank charges up his fist to make his next attack deal double his total attack damage and knock his 
    target up in the air. This ability will reset Blitzcrank\'s attack timer when cast.</string>
    <string name="StaticField" formatted="false">    PASSIVE: Every 2.5 seconds, Blitzcrank fires a lightning bolt at one random nearby enemy unit, dealing magic
    damage to it. This is not affected by cooldown reduction, and will not target enemies in stealth.\nACTIVE: Blitzcrank emits a wave of 
    electricity to deal magic damage to nearby enemies and silence them for 0.5 seconds. Activating it removes the passive lightning 
    bolts until Static Field becomes available again.</string>
    <string name="Blaze" formatted="false">    Brand\'s spells light his targets ablaze, dealing 2% of their maximum health as magic damage per second for 4 seconds, 
    for a total of 8%. Monsters take a maximum of 80 damage per second from Blaze.</string>
    <string name="Sear">    ACTIVE: Brand launches a fireball forward that deals magic damage to the first enemy it hits. 
    If the target is ablaze, the target will be stunned for 2 seconds.</string>
    <string name="PillarOfFlame" formatted="false">    ACTIVE: After a short delay, Brand blasts a target area, dealing magic damage to enemy 
    units within the area. Units that are ablaze take an additional 25% damage.</string>
    <string name="Conflagration">    ACTIVE: Brand conjures an instant blast at his target, dealing magic damage to it. If the target is ablaze, 
    the conflagration will also spread to nearby enemies.</string>
    <string name="Pyroclasm">    ACTIVE: Brand unleashes a devastating torrent of fire to a target that will bounce between enemies, dealing damage each 
    time it bounces. If a target is ablaze, Pyroclasm\'s next bounce will prioritize champions. It will bounce up to four
    times for a total of five hits, and can hit the same enemy up to three times.</string>
    <string name="Headshot" formatted="false">Every 8th / 7th / 6th basic attack deals 150% damage to a champion or 250% damage to a minion or monster. 
        Attacks from brush increase the attack counter by two instead of one.      </string>
    <string name="PiltoverPeacemaker" formatted="false">ACTIVE: After a 1 second casting time, Caitlyn fires a projectile that deals physical damage to all 
        targets it passes through. Each target hit after the first takes 10% less damage, down to a minimum of 50% of the original damage.      </string>
    <string name="YordleSnapTrap" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Caitlyn sets a trap at target location that activates after a brief delay. When an enemy champion
         comes within 67.5 range of the trap, the trap snares and deals magic damage to the enemy over 1.5 seconds, also revealing the enemy 
         for 9 seconds. \nCaitlyn can set up to 3 traps and each lasts 4 minutes. Traps are visible to both allies and enemies. If she sets 
         a trap when three are already placed, the oldest trap will deactivate itself.</string>
    <string name="NinetyCaliberNet">ACTIVE: Caitlyn fires a net, knocking herself back 400 units in the opposite direction. The net 
        will deal magic damage and slow the first enemy hit by 50%.</string>
    <string name="AceInTheHole">ACTIVE: Caitlyn channels for 1 second, providing vision of target enemy champion. She then fires a 3200-speed homing 
        projectile to the target, dealing physical damage to the first enemy champion it hits. Other enemy champions can intercept the bullet.</string>
    <string name="DeadlyCadence" formatted="false">Casting a spell causes any subsequent spellcasts within 5 seconds to cost 10% less mana, 
        stacking up to 5 times.</string>
    <string name="NoxiousBlast" formatted="false">ACTIVE: After a 0.6 second delay, Cassiopeia blasts the target 75-radius area. All enemies 
	    hit are poisoned and dealt magic damage over 3 seconds.\nCassiopeia is granted a movement speed boost for 3 seconds if Noxious Blast 
	    damages a champion.</string>
    <string name="Miasma">ACTIVE: Cassiopeia throws a growing cloud of poison to a target location, granting vision of the area and growing 
	    from a radius of 125 to 250 over 7 seconds. Enemies in the area are poisoned, becoming slowed and taking magic damage per second for 
	    2 seconds. Continual exposure renews the poison.</string>
    <string name="TwinFang" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Cassiopeia fires fangs at an enemy, dealing magic damage. If her target is poisoned, 
	    Twin Fang\'s cooldown is reduced to 0.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="PetrifyingGaze" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Cassiopeia blasts all enemies in a cone in front of her with her gaze, 
	    dealing magic damage to them. Enemies facing her when damaged are stunned for 2 seconds, while enemies facing away are slowed 
	    by 60% for 2 seconds instead. </string>
    <string name="Carnivore" formatted="false">Whenever Cho\'Gath kills a unit, he recovers 17 + (3 × level) health and 3.25 + (0.25 × level) mana.</string>
    <string name="Rupture" formatted="false">ACTIVE: After 0.625 seconds, Cho\'Gath makes spikes erupt in target 175-radius area, 
	    dealing magic damage and knocking up enemies for 1 second. Targets hit are slowed by 60% for a further 3 seconds after landing.</string>
    <string name="FeralScream" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Cho\'Gath roars, dealing magic damage and silencing all enemies in a cone area in front of him.</string>
    <string name="VorpalSpikes" formatted="false">TOGGLE: Whenever Cho\'Gath performs a basic attack, he will launch spikes dealing 
	    magic damage to enemies in a line in front of him.	    </string>
    <string name="Feast" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Cho\'gath devours target enemy, dealing true damage. If Feast kills the target, 
	    Cho\'Gath grows larger and gains extra health and basic attack range, stacking up to six times. Cho\'Gath loses half of these stacks, 
	    rounded up (Lost stacks being rounded up, thus, kept stacks rounded down), whenever he dies.\nFeast deals 1000 (+ 70% AP) true damage to 
	    minions and monsters.</string>
    <string name="HextechShrapnelShells" formatted="false">Corki\'s basic attacks deal additional true damage equal to 10% of his attack damage.
	     This bonus damage is not affected by critical hits, nor can it damage structures.</string>
    <string name="PhosphorusBomb" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Corki detonates a bomb over a 250-radius area. Enemies within the area upon cast 
	    take magic damage and are revealed for 6 seconds. Phosphorus Bomb cannot reveal stealthed enemies.</string>
    <string name="Valkyrie" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Corki flies to a target location at 650 speed, dropping bombs that leave up to 3 blazing 
	    patches along his path, depending on his distance travelled. The fire lasts for 2 seconds, damaging enemies that remain in the area 
	    every 0.5 seconds, for a maximum of 5 ticks of damage.</string>
    <string name="GatlingGun" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Corki activates his gatling gun, spraying bullets in a 35° cone in front 
	    of him for 4 seconds. Enemies inside the cone take physical damage and have their armor reduced by a stacking amount every 
	    0.5 seconds they remain in the gunfire, for a maximum of 8 applications of its damage and armor reduction. Gatling Gun does 
	    not hinder Corki\'s actions, and its cone will remain in front of him as he moves.</string>
    <string name="MissileBarrage" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Corki fires a missile in a line that explodes if it hits an enemy, 
	    damaging all enemies within 75 range.\nCorki reloads a missile every few seconds, up to a maximum of 7 stored at once; 
	    this reload time is affected by cooldown reduction. Upon death, Corki will respawn with 4 missiles. \nEvery third missile Corki 
	    fires becomes a Big One, dealing 50% additional damage and doubling its explosion range to 150. </string>
    <string name="Hemorrhage" formatted="false">Darius\' basic attacks and damaging abilities cause enemies to bleed 
	    for 12 / 15 / 18 / 21 / 24 / 27 / 30 / 33 / 36 (+ 30% Bonus AD) magic damage over 5 seconds. This stacks up to 
	    5 times for a maximum of 60 / 75 / 90 / 105 / 120 / 135 / 150 / 165 / 180 (+ 150% Bonus AD) magic damage over the duration.\n
	    Darius gains 5% movement speed for each bleeding enemy champion.</string>
    <string name="Decimate" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Darius swings his axe, dealing physical damage to all nearby enemies in a circle around him.\n
	    Champions in the outer half of the ability are struck by the blade, taking 50% additional damage.</string>
    <string name="CripplingStrike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Darius\' next basic attack deals additional damage and slows the target\'s 
	    movement and attack speed for 2 seconds.\nCrippling Strike\'s base cooldown is reduced by 1 second for each stack of Hemorrhage on the target.</string>
    <string name="Apprehend" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Darius gains armor penetration.\nACTIVE: Darius pulls in all enemies in front of him.</string>
    <string name="NoxianGuillotine" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Darius leaps to target enemy champion and strikes a lethal blow, dealing true damage.
	    For each stack of Hemorrhage on the target, Noxian Guillotine deals an additional 20% damage.\nWhen Noxian Guillotine kills the target, 
	    it can be recast within the next 12 seconds. This can occur multiple times in succession.</string>
    <string name="MoonsilverBlade" formatted="false">Diana gains 20% bonus attack speed. In addition, every third basic attack cleaves nearby 
	    enemies for 20 / 25 / 30 / 35 / 40 / 50 / 60 / 70 / 80 / 90 / 105 / 120 / 135 / 155 / 175 / 200 / 225 / 250 (+ 60% AP) additional magic damage.</string>
    <string name="CrescentStrike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Diana unleashes a bolt of lunar energy that travels in an arc. Enemies struck take 
	    magic damage and are afflicted with Moonlight, revealing them for 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="PaleCascade" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Diana gains a temporary shield for 5 seconds that absorbs incoming damage. 
	    She also creates three spheres that orbit her for up to 5 seconds. The spheres detonate on contact with an enemy unit, 
	    dealing magic damage to all nearby enemies.\nIf all three spheres detonate, the shield is reapplied and the duration is refreshed. 
	    This second shield stacks with the original shield.</string>
    <string name="Moonfall" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Diana draws in all nearby enemies to her location, slowing them for 2 seconds afterwards.</string>
    <string name="LunarRush" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Diana becomes the living embodiment of the vengeful moon, rushing at an enemy and dealing 
	    magic damage to it.\nWhen used to teleport to an enemy afflicted with Moonlight, Lunar Rush\'s cooldown is refreshed and the Moonlight 
	    debuff is consumed. All other enemies will have the Moonlight debuff removed regardless of whether they were the target of Lunar Rush.</string>
    <string name="AdrenalineRush" formatted="false">Dr. Mundo regains 0.3% of his maximum health each second.</string>
    <string name="InfectedCleaver" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Dr. Mundo hurls his cleaver in a line. The first enemy it hits takes magic 
	    damage equal to a percentage of its current health and is slowed by 40% for 2 seconds. In addition, Dr. Mundo is healed for an 
	    amount equal to half the health cost. Infected Cleaver has a minimum damage threshold, and a maximum damage cap versus monsters and minions.</string>
    <string name="BurningAgony" formatted="false">TOGGLE: While active, Dr. Mundo deals magic damage each second to nearby enemies and reduces the 
	    duration of crowd control effects on himself.</string>
    <string name="Masochism" formatted="false">ACTIVE: For 5 seconds, Dr. Mundo gains bonus attack damage plus additional attack damage for 
	    every 1% of his missing health.</string>
    <string name="Sadism" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Dr. Mundo regenerates a percentage of his maximum health over a period of 12 seconds. 
	    During this time his movement speed is increased.</string>
    <string name="WickedBlades" formatted="false">Draven\'s critical strikes deal 30 + (4 × level) bonus physical damage over 4 seconds. 
	    Spinning Axe also causes this effect even if it does not critically strike. If Wicked Blades is re-applied to a target, its duration 
	    is reset to 4 seconds and any damage not yet dealt is carried forward, increasing the amount of each tick of damage.</string>
    <string name="SpinningAxe" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Draven starts spinning his axe, making his next attack deal bonus physical damage 
	    equal to a percentage of his total attack damage. Wicked Blades is also applied to the target.\nThis axe will ricochet off the target 
	    high up into the air, landing 2 seconds later at a location determined by Draven\'s current movement direction and speed. If Draven 
	    catches it, Spinning Axe will be applied to his next attack.\nDraven can have up to two Spinning Axes readied at once.</string>
    <string name="BloodRush" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Draven gains increased movement speed for 1.5 seconds and increased attack speed for 
	    3 seconds. The movement speed bonus decreases rapidly over its duration.\nCatching a Spinning Axe will refresh Blood Rush\'s cooldown.</string>
    <string name="StandAside" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Draven throws his axes in a line. Enemies hit take physical damage, are knocked aside, 
	    and are slowed for 2 seconds afterwards.</string>
    <string name="WhirlingDeath" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Draven hurls two massive axes in a given direction, dealing physical damage to every 
	    enemy struck. \nUpon reaching the edge of the map, striking an enemy champion or upon the reactivation of Whirling Death, the axes 
	    will slowly come to a stop before changing direction and returning to Draven, dealing the same damage to every enemy struck on the way back. 
	    \nWhirling Death deals 8% less damage for each unit hit, down to a minimum of 40%. The damage reduction resets when the axes reverse direction.</string>
    <string name="SpiderSwarm" formatted="false">PASSIVE: When Elise\'s Human Form spells hit an enemy, she readies a Spiderling. While Elise is in 
	    Spider Form, she summons Spiderlings to attack nearby foes. The maximum number of Spiderlings increases with Spider Form\'s level.</string>
    <string name="EliseQ" formatted="false">Human Form: ACTIVE: Launches a blast of corrosive poison at target enemy, dealing magic damage equal 
	    to a base amount plus a percentage of target\'s current Health. Damage is capped against monsters.\n\nSpider Form: ACTIVE: Elise lunges 
	    to a target with a poisonous bite that deals magic damage equal to a base amount plus a percentage of the target\'s missing health. 
	    Damage is capped against monsters.</string>
    <string name="EliseW" formatted="false">Human Form: ACTIVE: Summons a venom-gorged Spiderling that moves to the target location and explodes, 
	    dealing magic damage to nearby enemies when it nears an enemy unit or after 3 seconds. If the Spiderling does not hit an enemy at the target 
	    location it will re-target itself and chase down a nearby enemy, prioritizing champions. The Spiderling\'s Movement Speed increases as it 
	    gets closer to its target.\n\nSpider Form: PASSIVE: Spiderlings gain bonus attack speed.\nACTIVE: Increases the attack speed of Elise and 
	    her Spiderlings for 3 seconds. While active, Elise is healed for a small amount when she or her spiderlings attack.</string>
    <string name="EliseE" formatted="false">Human Form: ACTIVE: Elise fires a web that stuns the first enemy hit for 1.5 seconds. 
	    It will also reveal enemies that are hit for a second.\n\nSpider Form: ACTIVE (ON ENEMY CAST): Elise reveals nearby enemy targets, 
	    while she and her Spiderlings lift up into the air, becoming untargetable for 1 second. She then descends upon the target enemy.\n
		ACTIVE (ON GROUND CAST): Elise reveals nearby enemy targets while she and her Spiderlings lift up into the air, becoming untargetable 
		for 2 seconds. During that time she can cast Rappel again to descend upon a nearby enemy. If no enemy is targeted within 2 seconds, 
		she will descend at her original location.</string>
    <string name="EliseR" formatted="false">TOGGLE: Elise transforms into a menacing spider, summoning her readied Spiderlings and granting access 
	    to arachnid abilities. While in Spider Form, Elise becomes melee and loses 425 range, deals bonus magic damage with her autoattacks and 
	    gains 10 movement speed.\nSPIDERLINGS: Spiderlings deal physical damage and take reduced damage from multi-target abilities.</string>
    <string name="ShadowWalk" formatted="false">PASSIVE: When out of combat for 6 seconds, Evelynn enters stealth only being able to be seen by 
	    enemy champions (within 700 range) or true sight. Evelynn regenerates 1% of her maximum mana every second while stealthed.\nCasting spells, 
	    taking damage or dealing damage reveals Evelynn for 6 seconds.</string>
    <string name="HateSpike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Evelynn fires a line of spikes through a nearby enemy, dealing magic damage to all 
	    enemy units in its path.</string>
    <string name="DarkFrenzy" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Evelynn\'s spell hits on enemy champions grant her a flat movement speed bonus for 3 seconds. 
	    This effect stacks up to 4 times.\nACTIVE: Evelynn removes all slows affecting her, gains increased movement speed for 3 seconds and ignores 
	    unit collision. Champion kills and assists refresh Dark Frenzy\'s cooldown.</string>
    <string name="Ravage" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Evelynn slashes a target twice, dealing magic damage with each strike. Evelynn then gains 
	    bonus attack speed for 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="AgonysEmbrace" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Evelynn impales all enemy units in target 250-radius area, dealing magic damage equal to a 
	    percentage of their current health and slowing their movement speed for 2 seconds.\nEvelynn siphons their pain, gaining a shield that 
	    grows in strength for each enemy champion hit and lasts up to 6 seconds.</string>
    <string name="RisingSpellForce" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Hitting a target with any of Ezreal\'s abilities increases his own attack speed by 10%. 
	    This effect lasts for 5 seconds and stacks up to 5 times.</string>
    <string name="MysticShot" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Ezreal fires a bolt of energy in a line that will deal physical damage and apply on-hit effects 
	    to the first enemy it hits. If it strikes an enemy unit, all of Ezreal\'s cooldowns will be reduced by 1 second.</string>
    <string name="EssenceFlux" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Ezreal fires a wave of energy in a line. Any enemy champions it passes through are dealt 
	    magic damage, while any allied champions it travels through have their attack speed increased for 5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="ArcaneShift" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Ezreal instantly teleports to a nearby target location and fires a homing arrow at the nearest 
	    enemy unit, dealing magic damage to it.</string>
    <string name="TrueshotBarrage" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Ezreal charges for 1 second to fire a powerful broad energy missile that travels in a line 
	    across the whole map, dealing magic damage to each enemy unit it passes through. It will deal 10% less damage for each subsequent target hit, 
	    down to a minimum of 30% damage dealt.</string>
    <string name="Dread" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Nearby enemy units have their magic resistance reduced by 10.</string>
    <string name="Terrify" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Afflicts a target unit with fear, preventing it from taking any actions and causing it to move 
	    around randomly at a slowed movement speed for the duration of the spell.</string>
    <string name="Drain" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Fiddlesticks creates a leash on a target enemy and channels for up to 5 seconds, dealing 
	    magic damage each second and healing himself for a percentage of the damage done. If the target leaves the range of Fiddlesticks\' leash, he will stop channeling.</string>
    <string name="DarkWind" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Fiddlesticks throws a crow that bounces to enemy units up to 5 times (5 hits in total), 
	    dealing magic damage (50% increased damage to minions and monsters) and silencing for 1.2 seconds with each strike. 
	    Dark Wind may strike the same target multiple times.</string>
    <string name="Crowstorm" formatted="false">ACTIVE: After channeling for 1.5 seconds, Fiddlesticks teleports to nearby target location with a 
	    murder of crows flying wildly around him for 5 seconds, dealing magic damage to all enemy units in the area each second.</string>
    <string name="Duelist" formatted="false">Fiora regenerates 7 + (Fiora\'s level) health over 6 seconds each time she deals physical damage. 
	    Striking champions will cause this effect to stack up to 4 times.</string>
    <string name="Lunge" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Fiora dashes forward to strike her target, dealing physical damage. Fiora can perform the 
	    dash a second time within 4 seconds at no mana cost.</string>
    <string name="Riposte" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Fiora\'s attack damage is increased.\nACTIVE: Fiora parries the next basic attack within 
	    1.5 seconds and deals magic damage to the attacker. Works against champions, monsters, and large minions.</string>
    <string name="BurstofSpeed" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Fiora gains additional attack speed for 3 seconds. Each basic attack or Lunge she lands during 
	    this time increases her movement speed for 3 seconds, stacking up to 3 times.\nKilling a champion refreshes the cooldown on Burst of Speed. 
	    Assists reduce the cooldown by half of the base amount.</string>
    <string name="BladeWaltz" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Fiora dashes around the battlefield—becoming untargetable in the process—dealing physical damage to 
	    random enemy champion(s) 5 times. Successive hits against the same target deal 25% damage. The first and last attack will be against the same target. 
	    Each strike applies on-hit effects.</string>
    <string name="NimbleFighter" formatted="false">Fizz\'s dexterity allows him to ignore unit collision and take 4 / 6 / 8 / 10 / 12 / 14 reduced physical 
	    damage from auto attacks.</string>
    <string name="UrchinStrike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Fizz dashes a fixed distance in the direction of the target enemy unit, dealing physical damage equal to 
	    his attack damage plus additional magic damage. The physical damage applies on-hit effects and the magic damage applies on-ability effects.</string>
    <string name="SeastoneTrident" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Fizz\'s autoattacks rend his target, dealing magic damage over 3 seconds that is increased based on a 
	    percentage of the target\'s missing health. This effect does not stack and multiple autoattacks will only refresh the duration. The total damage caps at 
	    300 against minions and monsters. \nACTIVE: Fizz\'s autoattacks are empowered for the next 5 seconds, dealing additional magic damage on-hit and applying 
	    Grievous Wounds (50% healing reduction) for 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="PlayfulTrickster" formatted="false">Playful: ACTIVE: Fizz hops onto his trident in a nearby location, becoming untargetable for 0.75 
	    seconds and gaining the ability to use Trickster before the effect ends.\nIf Fizz does not use Trickster, he will slam the ground below him, 
	    dealing magic damage and slowing nearby enemies within 250 range for 2 seconds.\n\nTrickster: ACTIVE: Fizz hops off from his trident to a nearby location, 
	    dealing magic damage to nearby enemies within 250 range. Trickster does not apply a slow.</string>
    <string name="ChumtheWaters" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Fizz throws a fish in a line that will bind itself onto the first enemy champion it hits. 
	    If it doesn\'t hit an enemy champion it will stay on an area, and it will stick to the first enemy champion that walks into the area. 
	    The fish will slow and reveal any enemy champion it is attached to.\n\nRegardless of position, after 1.5 seconds, a Shark will come out from the earth 
	    to eat the fish, dealing magic damage to all enemies within 250 range. The target is knocked up for 1 second, and all other enemies hit are knocked 
	    away from the center. All enemies hit are slowed for 1.5 seconds afterwards.</string>
    <string name="RunicSkin" formatted="false">Galio gains 50% of his total magic resistance as ability power.</string>
    <string name="ResoluteSmite" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Galio fires a concussive blast from his eyes to a target 235-radius area, 
	    dealing magic damage and slowing enemies hit for 2.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Bulwark" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Galio shields an allied champion for 4 seconds, increasing their armor and magic resistance. 
	    Each time that unit takes damage, Galio is healed. The heal is 20% weaker than the last for each consecutive hit.</string>
    <string name="RighteousGust" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Galio unleashes a gust of magical wind that deals magic damage to all enemies in its path. 
	    A directional draft remains for 5 seconds, increasing the movement speed of allies passing through it.</string>
    <string name="IdolofDurand" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Galio becomes a statue and channels for 2 seconds, taunting nearby foes and reducing 
	    incoming physical and magic damage by 50%. When the channel ends, Galio bursts out of his statue form, dealing magic damage to enemies within range. 
	    The damage is increased by 5% for each attack suffered while channeling (maximum 40%). If the channel is canceled, the damage radius is reduced to 
	    575 instead of 600.\nWhile channeling Idol of Durand, Galio can still cast Bulwark on allies within range.</string>
    <string name="GrogSoakedBlade" formatted="false">Gangplank\'s basic attacks apply a poison debuff for 3 seconds that can stack up to 3 times. 
	    Each stack deals 3 + (1 × level) magic damage per second and slows the target by 7%.</string>
    <string name="Parrrley" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Gangplank shoots a target enemy with his pistol, dealing physical damage. If it is killed with 
	    this ability, he gains extra gold and refunds half the mana cost. This ability can critically strike and applies on-hit effects, including his passive.</string>
    <string name="RemoveScurvy" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Gangplank eats a large amount of citrus fruit, instantly removing all crowd control 
	    effects on him, as well as healing himself.</string>
    <string name="RaiseMorale" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Gangplank\'s attack damage and movement speed are increased permanently.\nACTIVE: Gangplank fires 
	    into the air, disabling his passive boost but inspiring himself to gain additional attack damage and movement speed, with allied champions 
	    within range receiving half that amount, for 7 seconds.</string>
    <string name="CannonBarrage" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Gangplank signals his ship to fire a cannonball barrage upon a target 600-radius area for 7 seconds, 
	    granting vision of the area and slowing enemies inside it by 25% until 1.25 seconds after they exit the area.\n25 cannonballs randomly drop over the duration, 
	    each one dealing magic damage to enemies within a radius of 150.	    </string>
    <string name="Perseverance" formatted="false">If Garen has not taken damage from any source except minions in the last 9 seconds or affected by an enemy champion\'s 
	    abilities, he will start regenerating 0.4% of his maximum health per second.</string>
    <string name="DecisiveStrike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Garen breaks free from all slows affecting him and gains 35% movement speed for a few seconds. Additionally, 
	    his next basic attack within 4.5 seconds will deal additional physical damage and will silence his target.</string>
    <string name="Courage" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Garen\'s bonus armor and magic resistance are increased by 20%.\nACTIVE: Garen gains a defensive shield for a 
	    few seconds, reducing incoming damage by 30% and granting 30% crowd control reduction for the duration.</string>
    <string name="Judgment" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Garen rapidly spins his sword around his body for 3 seconds, dealing physical damage to enemies 
	    within range each second (minions and monsters take 75% damage). Judgment can critically strike dealing bonus damage.\nGaren ignores unit collision while 
	    spinning, but moves 20% slower when traveling directly through minions. Garen can deactivate Judgment early by activating the ability again after 0.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="DemacianJustice" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Garen calls upon the might of Demacia to attempt to execute an enemy champion, dealing magic 
	    damage plus additional damage based on his target\'s missing health.</string>
    <string name="HappyHour" formatted="false">Gragas takes a drink from his cask every time he uses an ability, restoring 2% of his 
	    maximum health over 4 seconds.</string>
    <string name="BarrelRoll" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Gragas rolls his cask to a location, which can be activated again to explode or will 
	    explode on its own after 5 seconds. Enemies within 350 range of the cask take magic damage and have their attack speed reduced for 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="DrunkenRage" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Gragas guzzles down brew from his cask, gaining mana and starting a 1 second channel. 
	    If the channel is completed he gains additional mana and becomes empowered, increasing attack damage and reducing physical 
	    and magic damage taken for 20 seconds.</string>
    <string name="BodySlam" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Gragas charges forward, stopping the charge if he collides with an enemy unit. 
	    Enemy units in an area around Gragas then take magic damage and are slowed by 35% for 2.5 seconds. Damage is split amongst targets hit.</string>
    <string name="ExplosiveCask" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Gragas throws his cask to target 400-radius area, damaging and knocking back 
	    enemies in the area up to 600 distance, and briefly gives vision within 500 range.</string>
    <string name="TrueGrit" formatted="false">Graves gains 1 / 2 / 3 bonus armor and magic resistance every second he remains in combat.
	     This bonus stacks up to 10 times. Graves is considered in combat if he has dealt or received damage in the last 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="Buckshot" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Graves fires three bullets in a cone, dealing physical damage to all enemies in their path. 
	    Enemies at close range can be hit by multiple projectiles, but each bullet beyond the first will deal only 35% damage.</string>
    <string name="SmokeScreen" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Graves fires a smoke canister at the target area, 
	    dealing magic damage upon landing and creating a cloud of smoke 250 wide for 4 seconds. Enemies 
	    inside the smoke cloud will be slowed and will have their vision reduced by 675 range; 
	    everything else will look like it is in the Fog of War.</string>
    <string name="Quickdraw" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Graves dashes forward, gaining an attack speed boost for 4 seconds. 
	    Using autoattacks on enemy units, but not structures, lowers the cooldown of Quickdraw by 1 second each autoattack.    </string>
    <string name="CollateralDamage" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Graves fires an explosive shell in a straight line, 
	    dealing heavy physical damage to the first champion it hits (also damages non-champion enemies whilst in flight). 
	    After hitting a champion or reaching the end of its range, the shell explodes dealing physical damage in a cone behind the target.</string>
    <string name="Warpath" formatted="false">Hecarim ignores unit collision and gains bonus attack damage equal to 
	    10 / 12.5 / 15 / 17.5 / 20 / 22.5 / 25 % of his bonus movement speed.   </string>
    <string name="Rampage" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Hecarim cleaves nearby enemies, dealing physical damage. 
	    This skill deals only 66% damage to minions and monsters. \n\nIf Hecarim damages at least one enemy unit with this attack, 
	    he gains a stack of Rampage, reducing the base cooldown of this skill by 1 second for 8 seconds. This effect can stack up to 2 times.    </string>
    <string name="SpiritofDread" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Hecarim surrounds himself with the spirit of dread for 4 seconds, 
	    dealing magic damage per second to all enemies within its reach. Additionally, Hecarim is healed for 20% of the 
	    damage dealt by any source to enemies within the area. Healing from damage dealt to minions is capped per cast.    </string>
    <string name="DevastatingCharge" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Hecarim gains 75% movement speed over the course of 3 seconds, 
	    starting with initial 25% upon cast, and ending one second afterward. While Hecarim is charging, 
	    he gains 150 extra attack range (325 total). His next attack knocks the target back, dealing physical 
	    damage based on how far Hecarim has traveled during Devastating Charge\'s duration.\n\nIf Hecarim\'s target is beyond narrow 
	    terrain, Hecarim will leap over the terrain to his target.        </string>
    <string name="OnslaughtofShadows" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Hecarim summons spectral riders and charges forward 
	    with them in a line, dealing magic damage to enemies in their path. Enemies within range of where Hecarim 
	    stops will flee in terror for 1 second.\n\nThe wave of spectral riders will travel the maximum distance possible in the 
	    direction of cast, regardless of where Hecarim himself stops.        </string>
    <string name="TechmaturgicalRepairBots" formatted="false">Heimerdinger gives himself and nearby allied structures and units 
	    10 / 15 / 20 / 25 health regeneration per 5 seconds.    </string>
    <string name="H28GEvolutionturret" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Heimerdinger constructs a Turret that fires at nearby enemies, 
	    dealing magic damage with its attacks (half damage to towers and inhibitors). Heimerdinger stores enough 
	    parts for a new turret every 25 seconds, affected by cooldown reduction. Turrets disappear automatically 
	    when Heimerdinger dies. Turrets receive upgrades and transform with every ability rank.\n\nTurret Health: 260 + (15 × level)\n
	    Turret Range: 525\nTurret Attack Speed: 1.25 (1.85 after 6 seconds)\nSight Radius: 625    </string>
    <string name="HextechMicroRockets" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Heimerdinger fires long range rockets that target and deal magic 
	    damage to the 3 enemy units closest to him.    </string>
    <string name="CH1ConcussionGrenade" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Heimerdinger lobs a grenade at a target location, 
	    dealing magic damage and blinding to enemy units within 250 range. Enemies within 100 range are stunned for 1.5 seconds.    </string>
    <string name="UPGRADE" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Heimerdinger gains cooldown reduction.\n\nACTIVE: All active 
	    Evolution Turrets are healed for 100% of their maximum health. Also for the next 6 seconds all of his abilities 
	    are improved. His turrets turn blue and start to fire slowing frost shots. Newly created turrets also have this 
	    property. He now fires 5 Hextech Micro-Rockets instead of 3 and the missile speed on CH-1 Concussion Grenade is 
	    increased from 750 to 1000.        </string>
    <string name="IonianFervor" formatted="false">For each nearby enemy champion, Irelia reduces the duration of stuns, 
	    slows, taunts, fears, snares, immobilizes, blinds and silences.    </string>
    <string name="Bladesurge" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Irelia dashes forward to strike her target, 
	    dealing physical damage. This applies on-hit effects. If it kills the target, Bladesurge\'s 
	    cooldown refreshes and refunds 35 mana.    </string>
    <string name="HitenStyle" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Irelia\'s autoattacks restore health.\n\nACTIVE: Irelia\'s autoattacks 
	    deal additional true damage for 6 seconds. Hiten Style\'s passive on-hit health restore is doubled for the duration.    </string>
    <string name="EquilibriumStrike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Irelia pierces her target, dealing magic damage and slowing the 
	    target by 60% for the duration. If the target has a higher health % than Irelia, she stuns the target for the same duration instead.    </string>
    <string name="TranscendentBlades" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Irelia summons 4 spirit blades and fires one in a line towards the cursor, 
	    dealing physical damage to all enemies it passes through. Irelia is healed for 25% of the damage dealt to champions and 10% 
	    of the damage dealt to minions and monsters.\n\nWithin the next 15 seconds, Transcendent Blades can be used 
	    up to three more times at no cost.</string>
    <string name="Tailwind" formatted="false">The wind aids Janna\'s allies, increasing their movement speed
	     by 3%. This bonus is lost while Janna is dead.    </string>
    <string name="HowlingGale" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Janna summons a mighty whirlwind. For the next 
	    three seconds, she can then reactivate the spell to release the storm. On release the storm will 
	    fly in the direction it was cast, dealing magic damage to enemies and knocking them into the air. 
	    The damage done, knock up duration and distance traveled by the whirlwind increase for each second 
	    it channels.    </string>
    <string name="Zephyr" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Janna is aided by a wind elemental, 
	    gaining movement speed and ignoring unit collision.\n\nACTIVE: Janna launches the elemental 
	    to deal magic damage and slow an enemy\'s movement speed for 3 seconds. She loses the ability\'s 
	    passive benefits while it is on cooldown.        </string>
    <string name="EyeoftheStorm" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Janna surrounds a target ally with a wind 
	    shield that absorbs incoming damage for 5 seconds. While the shield persists, the target will 
	    also gain an attack damage bonus.\n\nThis ability can be used on turrets. If a shielded 
	    turret kills an enemy champion, Janna will receive the kill.        </string>
    <string name="Monsoon" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Janna emits a powerful blast of wind, knocking back 
	    enemies within 875 range and then channels, releasing curing winds that heal allies within 875 
	    range every half-second for 4 seconds.    </string>
    <string name="MartialCadence" formatted="false">Jarvan IV\'s first attack on a target deals 6% / 8% / 10% 
	    of their current health as bonus physical damage. This caps at 400 damage. This effect cannot occur 
	    on the same target more than once every 6 seconds.    </string>
    <string name="DragonStrike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Jarvan IV extends his lance in a straight line, 
	    dealing physical damage and lowering the armor of all enemies hit for 3 seconds. Additionally, if it 
	    encounters his Demacian Standard, it will pull Jarvan to it, knocking up enemies along his path for 
	    0.75 seconds.    </string>
    <string name="GoldenAegis" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Jarvan IV slows enemies within range for 2 
	    seconds and shields himself for up to 5 seconds. The shield gains strength for each enemy 
	    champion within range upon activation.    </string>
    <string name="DemacianStandard" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Permanently grants Jarvan IV bonus armor 
	    and attack speed.\n\nACTIVE: Jarvan IV throws a Demacian flag to the target location, 
	    dealing magic damage to enemies within 75 range. The flag will remain for 8 seconds, providing 
	    vision in a radius of 700 and an aura that increases the attack speed of allies within a radius of 600.       </string>
    <string name="Cataclysm" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Jarvan IV leaps to an enemy champion, 
	    dealing physical damage to it and creating a 325-radius circle of impassable terrain around 
	    themselves. This circle lasts for 3.5 seconds and also grants sight within 825 range. Jarvan IV 
	    can prematurely destroy the impassable terrain by activating this ability again.    </string>
    <string name="RelentlessAssault" formatted="false">Basic attacks increase Jax\'s attack speed by 
	    4% / 6% / 8% / 10% / 12% / 14%. Relentless Assault lasts for 2.5 seconds and stacks up to 
	    6 times for a maximum of 24% / 36% / 48% / 60% / 72% / 84%.    </string>
    <string name="LeapStrike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Jax leaps to target unit, dealing physical damage 
	    if the target is an enemy.    </string>
    <string name="Empower" formatted="false">ACTIVE: Jax\'s next basic attack or Leap Strike 
	    within the next 10 seconds deals additional magic damage. Empower resets the autoattack timer.    </string>
    <string name="CounterStrike" formatted="false">ACTIVE: For up to 2 seconds, Jax dodges all 
	    basic attacks and takes 25% less damage from area of effect abilities. At the end of the 
	    duration or if Counter Strike is activated again, Jax deals physical damage and stuns nearby 
	    enemies for 1 second. This spell deals 20% additional damage for each attack dodged to a maximum 
	    of 100% increased damage.    </string>
    <string name="GrandmastersMight" formatted="false">PASSIVE: Jax deals additional magic damage on 
	    every third basic attack. The counter will reset if he does not attack for 2.5 seconds.\n\n
	    ACTIVE: Jax gains bonus armor and magic resistance for 8 seconds.        </string>
    <string name="ChampionsButton">Champions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_champs">Champions</string>
    <string name="title_section3">lore</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Abilities</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Statistics</string>
    <string name="title_activity_champion_page">ChampionName</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Other</string>
    <string name="title_activity_stats">StatsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ability_fragment">AbilityFragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lore_fragment">LoreFragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ability_details">AbilityDetails</string>

    <string-array name="ChampNames">
        <item>Aatrox</item>
        <item>Ahri</item>
        <item>Akali</item>
        <item>Alistar</item>
        <item>Amumu</item>
        <item>Anivia</item>
        <item>Annie</item>
        <item>Ashe</item>
        <item>Blitzcrank</item>
        <item>Brand</item>
        <item>Caitlyn</item>
        <item>Cassiopeia</item>
        <item>Cho\'Gath</item>
        <item>Corki</item>
        <item>Darius</item>
        <item>Diana</item>
        <item>Dr. Mundo</item>
        <item>Draven</item>
        <item>Elise</item>
        <item>Evelynn</item>
        <item>Ezreal</item>
        <item>Fiddlesticks</item>
        <item>Fiora</item>
        <item>Fizz</item>
        <item>Galio</item>
        <item>Gangplank</item>
        <item>Garen</item>
        <item>Gragas</item>
        <item>Graves</item>
        <item>Hecarim</item>
        <item>Heimerdinger</item>
        <item>Irelia</item>
        <item>Janna</item>
        <item>Jarvan IV</item>
        <item>Jax</item>
        <item>Jayce</item>
        <item>Karma</item>
        <item>Karthus</item>
        <item>Kassadin</item>
        <item>Katarina</item>
        <item>Kayle</item>
        <item>Kennen</item>
        <item>Kha\'Zix</item>
        <item>Kog\'Maw</item>
        <item>LeBlanc</item>
        <item>Lee Sin</item>
        <item>Leona</item>
        <item>Lissandra</item>
        <item>Lucian</item>
        <item>Lulu</item>
        <item>Lux</item>
        <item>Malphite</item>
        <item>Malzahar</item>
        <item>Maokai</item>
        <item>Master Yi</item>
        <item>Miss Fortune</item>
        <item>Mordekaiser</item>
        <item>Morgana</item>
        <item>Nami</item>
        <item>Nasus</item>
        <item>Nautilus</item>
        <item>Nidalee</item>
        <item>Nocturne</item>
        <item>Nunu</item>
        <item>Olaf</item>
        <item>Orianna</item>
        <item>Pantheon</item>
        <item>Poppy</item>
        <item>Quinn</item>
        <item>Rammus</item>
        <item>Renekton</item>
        <item>Rengar</item>
        <item>Riven</item>
        <item>Rumble</item>
        <item>Ryze</item>
        <item>Sejuani</item>
        <item>Shaco</item>
        <item>Shen</item>
        <item>Shyvana</item>
        <item>Singed</item>
        <item>Sion</item>
        <item>Sivir</item>
        <item>Skarner</item>
        <item>Sona</item>
        <item>Soraka</item>
        <item>Swain</item>
        <item>Syndra</item>
        <item>Talon</item>
        <item>Taric</item>
        <item>Teemo</item>
        <item>Thresh</item>
        <item>Tristana</item>
        <item>Trundle</item>
        <item>Tryndamere</item>
        <item>Twisted Fate</item>
        <item>Twitch</item>
        <item>Udyr</item>
        <item>Urgot</item>
        <item>Varus</item>
        <item>Vayne</item>
        <item>Veigar</item>
        <item>Vi</item>
        <item>Viktor</item>
        <item>Vladimir</item>
        <item>Volibear</item>
        <item>Warwick</item>
        <item>Wukong</item>
        <item>Xerath</item>
        <item>Xin Zhao</item>
        <item>Yorick</item>
        <item>Zed</item>
        <item>Ziggs</item>
        <item>Zilean</item>
        <item>Zyra</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="userRegion">
        <item name="na">North America</item>
        <item name="euw">Europe West</item>
        <item name="eune">Europe Northeast</item>
        <item name="br">Brazil</item>
        <!--
        <item name="ru">Russia</item>
        <item name="tr">Turkey</item>
        <item name="las">Latin America South</item>
        <item name="lan">Latin America North</item>
        <item name="oc">Oceania</item>
        -->
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="transitionEffect">
        <item>Accordion</item>
		<item>Cube In</item>
		<item>Cube Out</item>
		<item>Flip Horizontal</item>
		<item>Flip Vertical</item>
		<item>Rotate Down</item>
		<item>Rotate Up</item>
		<item>Stack</item>
		<item>Standard</item>
		<item>Tablet</item>
		<item>Zoom In</item>
		<item>Zoom Out</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="userRegionValues">
        <item name="na">NA</item>
        <item name="euw">EUW</item>
        <item name="eune">EUNE</item>
        <item name="br">BR</item>
        <!--
        <item name="ru">ru</item>
        <item name="tr">tr</item>
        <item name="las">las</item>
        <item name="lan">lan</item>
        <item name="oc">oc</item>
        -->
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="drawerStuff">
        <item>Champions</item>
        <item>Summoner Lookup</item>
        <item>Jungle Timers</item>
        <item>Free Champion Rotation</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_profile">ProfileActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_match_history_fragment">MatchHistoryFragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_view_test">ListViewTest</string>
    <string name="title_activity_passive_popup">PassivePopup</string>
    <string name="title_activity_wpopup">WPopup</string>
    <string name="title_activity_epopup">EPopup</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rpopup">RPopup</string>
    <string name="title_activity_match_history">MatchHistoryActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_match_fragment_one">MatchFragmentOne</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile_main">ProfileMainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile_fragment">ProfileFragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lifetime_stats_fragment">LifetimeStatsFragment</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_drawer">DrawerActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_guides_fragment">GuidesFragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_jungle_timers">JungleTimers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_jungle_timer_selector">JungleTimerSelector</string>
    <string name="title_activity_jungle_timers_tt">JungleTimersTT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_free_week">FreeWeekActivity</string>

</resources>